In fires, we create
something new
We're strangers again
Strangers again
In fires, the chill melts away
All we need is a reason
We just need a reason
We can start all over again
Follow secret signs to find our way home
Often hidden
by leaves that fell out of boredom
The signs are steeped
in me and you
Songs are written
with a new fire inside
A new fire
In fires, we create
something new
We're strangers again
Strangers again
In fires, the chill melts away
All we need is a reason
We just need a reason
Sparks will remain
overhead
You're my heart and
I'm your fire
Fire
In fires, we create
something new
We're strangers again
Strangers again
In fires, the chill melts away
All we need is a reason
We just need a reason